KHANH VU QUOC

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

SUMMARY

I am a student in my final year of university, but I had over one-year experience as a backend developer in this industry. As a software developer, I have been finding solutions to solve issues and optimize them whenever possible. Furthermore, collaboration, teamwork, listen to leaders are my capability.

REACH ME AT:

Phone: (+84) 376-371-468

Email: vukhanhh02092001@gmail.com

Address: Tran Van On Street, Phu Hoa District, Thu Dau Mot City, Vietnam

WORK EXPERIENCE

March 2022- Present

Dai Phat Dat I Le Hong Phong, Phu Hoa, Thu Dau Mot City

Garage Management Software

Backend .Net developer | October 2022 - Ferbruary 2023

- According to the analysis of the team leader and then write API to solve the problem. Apply native queries in projects to tackle highly difficult business. Finally, the production is currently being used by the client.
- Set up the structure folder according to the clean architecture by myself.
- Create the Apis implement from REST API Design Best Practices.
- Collaboration with Front-end developers to update and create API.

Digital Library Software

Backend .Net developer | June 2022 - September 2022

- Join the team leader to analyze business about library management. In addition, using Entity Framework to interact with SQL Server to save and query data to solve the relative problem.
 As a result, the production is running in roughly 70 primary, junior, and high schools nationwide.
- Pick up user stories, analyze them, discuss them with the team leader to tackle them, and write documentation to clarify my API.
- Invoke in a Scrum software development process.

ACADEMIC BACKGROUND

Thu Dau Mot University of Software Engineering

- Participated in an ICPC programming contest.
- Solved 300 problems on Codeforces.
 - https://codeforces.com/submissions/Khanhzuu/page/1
- TOEIC: 825/990
 - https://github.com/KhanhVu21/Certificates/blob/main/toeic.jpg
- During the research and work on the project time, I had a structured folder for the backend .NET project according to clean architecture created on my own.
 - https://github.com/KhanhVu21/Backend_Application.git
- Team-worked on a lot of projects for 4 years with skills such as report writing, database design, and product presentation.
- GPA: 3.0/4.0

SKILLS

Soft skills: Communication, teamwork, collaboration, and

Framework: .NET CORE, ReactJS, Expressjs.

Programming languages: C#, <u>JavaScript</u>, C++, Java.

Other languages: HTML, CSS

Databases: MSSQL, MySQL, MongoDB.

Additional skills: GitHub

Ideas: JetBrains Rider, Visual Studio Code, Visual Studio,

DataGrip.